Guide to the Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca records, 1908-1972.
Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca records, 1908-1972
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca records, 1908-1972
41-6-1680
Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca.
0.8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, reports, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Official records of the Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca including correspondence and other materials relating to membership, publicity notices for social events, fund raising, meetings minutes and reports, the Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs, and scholarships.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Official records of the Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca including correspondence relating to membership and publicity notices for social events, correspondence and records relating to fund raising and fund raising events, meetings, the Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs, contributions to scholarship funds and scholarship winners. Also included are minutes and reports from Club meetings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Women's Club of Ithaca.; Cornell University.; Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs.
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, 1944-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Broadsides, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- News releases, 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- News letters, 1953-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Clippings, 1949-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes (record book), 1949-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1956-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Resolutions, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Financial records and reports, 1954-1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Reports, 1956-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Membership lists, 1952-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Officers and committee members, 1945-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Lists, 1945-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Schedules and agendas, 1944-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Seating charts, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Constitution and bylaws, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Pamphlets and handbook, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Memorabilia, 1915, 1960s, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Secretary's book, 1908-1912 (Box 2, Volume 1)
- Secretary's book, 1912-1914 (Box 2, Volume 2)
- Minutes, 1915-1918 (Box 2, Volume 3)
- "99 sandwiches" (pamphlet), 1915 (Box 2, Volume 4)
- "Report of the University Faculty ... in Regard to the Office of Adviser of Women" (pamphlet), 1917 (Box 2, Volume 5)
- Secretary's reports and minutes, 1918-1921 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, June 21, 1910-April 26, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, April 27-May 1, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, May 2, 1916-May 9, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, May 9-November 29, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, November 30, 1917-January 24, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, January 28-March 1, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, March 2-17, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, March 18-April 10, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, April 11, 1918-June 21, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1915-June 26, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)